Hi, welcome to Wendy's. Would you like to try a blazon bacon at it today?
Oh no, I'm good.
May I take your order please?
Can I have a nappo, pecan and chicken salad?
Would you like to make it combo?
No. I mean, what does include in combo? Fries and drinks?
Yeah, you can take potatoes, whatever you want.
What kind of drink? Can I take lemonade with it?
Yeah, you can take it.
Okay, so...
You want to make it combo?
Yeah, yeah.
You want strawberry, watermelon and the original?
No, the lemonade.
Yeah, you want strawberry, lemonade, original and the watermelon?
Give me watermelon.
Would that be medium or large combo?
Medium.
Anything else for you?
So, what's other than fries? Should I take potatoes or something like that?
Yeah, you can take it.
Okay, alright. Can I have that?
So, you want sour cream and chai, plain cheese potato, bacon and cheese or chili cheese potato?
No, bacon.
So, which potato do you want then?
Okay, give me sour cream and chai, plain cheese potato.
Okay, anything else for you?
No.
Drive up, thank you.
Thank you.