Hi, welcome to Wendy's. Would you like to try a new blizzard bacon eater today?
No, that's okay.
May I take you out of the place?
Yeah, can I get a 10 piece nugget meal?
Plum sauce is fine for the dipping?
Uh, barbecue sauce please.
And cooked to drink?
What are you drinking?
The strawberry lemonade light ice please.
Would that be a medium or large combo?
Just regular please.
Anything else for you?
Yep, can I also get a number one with no onions?
Cooked to drink?
Cooked to drink, no ice please.
Can I make the fries a poutine?
Yeah, you can.
Anything else for you?
I'm also going to get a bacon and cheese baked potato.
Okay.
And just the burger of the Dave's Burger, the Dave's single, sorry.
And that one's only lettuce, tomato and cheese.
Just the sandwich, right?
Yes, just the sandwich.
So it's pretty much, I'm sorry I'm going to make it simple, it's pretty much no onions and no sauce.
Sorry.
So it's the sandwich you want only tomato and lettuce, right?
Pickles and cheese.
That's what I said, I was trying to fix it, sorry.
Pickles and cheese. Anything else for you?
Nope, I believe that's everything.
Thank you.