Hi, welcome to WENI, would you like to try our blazing baked nutrient combo today?
Hi, can I, hello?
Grilled chicken?
Uh, no thanks.
I'm sorry, what can I get for you?
Can I get a small caramel apple crosti?
Small apple caramel crosti?
Anything else for you?
Can I get a JVC with extra lettuce, extra tomato, extra onion?
Okay, anything else for you?
Can I get a junior hamburger with lettuce, extra tomato, extra onion?
So junior hamburger with the light ketchup?
Yeah, ketchup, extra lettuce, extra tomato, extra onion, and no pickle.
No pickle, extra onion, extra tomato, and extra lettuce?
And light mayo and ketchup, you said?
Yeah, light mayo, just regular ketchup.
Okay, sure, anything else for you?
No, not extra mayo though.
Oh, I'm sorry, sorry, sorry, here you go.
Anything else for you?
And can I get a large ice water?
Large ice water?
That's everything.
Okay, thank you.