Hi, welcome to Wendy's. Would you like to try a new Blizzard Baconator today?
No, I'm okay. She's here. What do you want? Chicken strips?
Hi, can I get the...
Do you have like a five piece strip combo?
We do have three pieces. I can give you on the side, like two strips on the side.
And then how much for the crispy for the combo?
Just let me try.
So, it's 16.15.
Okay. Yeah, that's fine. I'll take the chicken strips combo.
Do you want to go with them?
Do you have chicken strips? Oh, you have nuggets?
Okay, so I'll take the three piece combo and then the nugget.
The four piece nugget combo.
So, for the nuggets we do have five piece and ten nuggets. I can make it combo.
No, I'll take the kids meal, the four piece nugget.
Okay.
And then just a...