Hi, welcome to Wendy's. Would you like to try a new blazon baconator today?
What do you have? New?
It's the new blazon baconator. You want to try it?
New blazon. How much is it?
What do you got on top? Steak?
I'm sorry?
Do we have steak on top? No steak.
No. It's a beef sandwich. Oh, beef?
Yeah. How much is it?
If you would like a combo, it's gonna be, one second, let me tell you.
It's gonna be $13.78 including tax.
And if you want just a sandwich, that's gonna be $9.59 including tax.
No, give me a combo.
You want a combo? Yeah.
Coke to drink?
Coke? No. I need, I need Fanta.
Medium or large combo? No, Fanta.
Okay, and combo would be medium or large? Medium.
Anything else for you?
What did I say? I need five nuggets.
Five nuggets with plum sauce? Yeah.
Anything else for you? That's it.
Thank you.