Hi, welcome to Wendy's, would you like to try our new Blasian baked nectarina combo
today?
No, actually I like to order chicken strips.
Chicken strips combo?
Yes.
With plum sauce?
Coke today?
Coke or water?
One bottle of water.
Okay.
And one empty glass, I think.
One empty glass?
Yes.
Okay.
The price would be medium or large?
No, I need chicken strips.
Only strips and bottled water, right?
Chicken nuggets, what it's called, nuggets or strips?
Chicken strips and empty cup and then you want bottled water, right?
Yeah.
How many in one order?
Three strips, but you can add extra if you want, just like us.
Give me six.
So I'll give you two orders.
How many, two?
Two orders is like six, three in each.
Yes.
I need one combo and one just on the side.
One combo?
Yes.
I need one combo and three on the side, like one, two, three, yes.
Okay.
The combo is with fries and a water bottle, right?
Yes.
All right.
I don't need a, okay, you know, give me six chicken nuggets.
I don't need a fries.
I need one bottle of water.
Okay.
Done.
Thank you.