Hi there, welcome to Wendy's, would you like to try our Blazing Baconator today?
Hello.
Hi.
Can I have the number, number 6.
Number 6 combo?
Yeah.
Coke the drink.
One other drink here.
So we have a lot of drinks, options.
We have root beer, we have over a hundred drinks.
The boy always said Coke.
So Coke, Diet Coke, Sprite, Ice Tea, Fanta.
Give me Ice Tea.
Ok, so number 6 combo.
Is Ice Tea.
Yeah, a lot of ice.
Sorry?
A lot of ice in the drink.
No ice?
Lots of ice in the drink.
Extra ice?
Ok, would you like to make your combo medium or large?
What?
Would you like to upsize your combo to medium or large?
What do you mean upsize my combo?
The price and the drink, do you want to upsize it?
Do they give you small price and small drink to come with?
Yup.
When since is this?
Sorry?
I have a Wendy's right at my house.
I'm hard inside.
I throw one and they don't do that.
The small is the regular size.
No, it's ok.
Just give me that.
Give me that guys.
Ok, anything else?
No.
Thank you.